Haley Morgan

Engineer with a constant drive for self-development, and a passion for learning new languages, technologies, and software design principles. Emphasis on work ethic, interpersonal skills, teamwork, and continuous code testing.

Location Watertown, MA **Phone** (774)-262-7555

Email haleymorgan3264@gmail.com

GitHub h-morgan

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/haleymorgan

Personal haleyemorgan.com

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, Python, SQL, JSON, HTML, CSS, C++

Frameworks/Libraries: Bootstrap, React, jQuery

Tooling: Git/GitHub, VS Code, Microsoft Office Apps

Other: Engineering, technical writing, debugging, teamwork, communication, presentations

PROJECTS

Flashcards Application: built a flashcard web app using React on the frontend and a database backend to generate a random flashcard on button click, to help study for exams.

Agassiz Village Website: worked with local non-profit organization to update, edit, and maintain events pages on their website as needed in response to their requests.

Personal Website: created a personal portfolio website from scratch using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript and deployed the site using FTP, as a place to store projects and track my learning progress.

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2018 - PRESENT

Information Privacy and Compliance Analyst

Clark University; Worcester, MA

- Work with end users to continuously collect and analyze functional requirements and use cases for all enterprise projects, evolving solutions as needed
- Develop and maintain a system to triage and monitor malicious phishing emails using regex rules written in the YARA language to decrease exposure of compromised accounts
- Assist in security testing response efforts to ensure applications are as secure and stable as possible, upholding the CIA triad

APR 2017 - OCT 2018

Civil Engineer

Tetra Tech; Marlborough, MA

- Performed site and system redesign through continuous iterations as member of an interdisciplinary team to eliminate costly and unnecessary complexities
- Applied technical knowledge to design Department of Defense (DoD) and USAID international bases/sites using AutoCAD Civil3D
- Maintained Active Secret Security clearance for ability to work on classified projects

EDUCATION

MAY 2016 Worcester Polytechnic Institute (WPI)

Bachelor of Science, Civil Engineering

JAN 2018 – PRES. Quinsigamond Community College (QCC) & Online

Computer Science coursework

CERTIFICATES

JUL 2019 JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures (300 hours) - FreeCodeCamp

MAR 2019 Responsive Web Design (300 hours) - FreeCodeCamp

MAR 2017 – FEB 2018 Python for Data Science - DataCamp